Language

Recent email

Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated: 05-09-2019

Introduction
------------

This privacy policy describes how we treat personal information and data when you use the online web applications. In this Privacy Policy, "we", "us", "our" and other similar references mean our Service and "you" and "your" and other similar references mean any particular user of the Service. This Privacy Policy describes how we uses personal information of users collected through our Service ("Personal Information").

This policy applies immediately to users who utilize the Service on or after the Effective Date and on the Effective Date to users who utilize the Service before the Effective Date. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy and the applicable User Agreement, please exit, and do not access or use, the Service.

Please contact us if you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy. You can reach us online by using feedback page or email.

Personal Information
--------------------

We do not collect personally that identifies you to the Service, such as your user name, email address and IP address. The service works anonymously, so we do not keep track of what actions users are taking.

Also you choose to input Personal Data as part of images, comments, and other content, information, and materials that you post to or through the Service.

Cookies
-------

We may send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. We may use cookies to improve the quality of our service. We use cookies to remember your personal settings, such as sound or pop-up notifications, or others that are created for your convenience. You can disable cookies on your device, but this may make some service features unavailable, such as sound or pop-up notifications of new events.

Cookies are also used by third-party services such as AD networks and Google analytics. You can read more about it here [privacy policy of Google](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/ "privacy policy of Google")

Analytics data
--------------

We use Google analytics to know how many users are using the Service.

Ad serving
----------

We use the Google Adsense technology to provide advertisements of interest to you within our Services. Refer to the Google Adsense policy.

External links
--------------

In case you leave our website by using a link to an external website, you are connect to another internet provider. These links lead to content that is not stored on our own servers.

Different privacy policies may apply to the websites to which the external links lead may contain. We, therefore, recommend to check these privacy policies by visiting the homepage of the respective online service or (if necessary) contact the controller of the respective website.

Security
--------

We use modern security methods to communicate with the service. Also, all data passing through the service uses a secure connection.

Privacy Policy Changes
----------------------

Like all operators, from time to time we can change the rules and make the service as attractive to users as possible. Therefore, we recommend that you check this page from time to time for policy changes if it matters to you.

Feedback | [Blog](https://emailfake.com/blog) | [Privacy Policy](https://emailfake.com/privacy-policy)
